export const slot_1_august_19_2023 = [
  {
    _id: "1",
    topic: "LCM and HCF",
    category: "Numerical-Ability",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question: "What is the sum of LCM and HCF of 5/18, 35/9, and 15/63?",
    options: {
      A: "1475/252",
      B: "1475/126",
      C: "625/252",
      D: "625/126",
    },
    correct_option: "B",
    solution: "The sum of LCM and HCF is 1475/126.",
  },
  {
    _id: "2",
    topic: "Reciprocal and Fractions",
    category: "Numerical-Ability",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question:
      "The reciprocal of a fraction is more than itself by 21/240. How much is the difference between the possible values of the fraction more than 2?",
    options: {
      A: "1/15",
      B: "1/16",
      C: "1/240",
      D: "1/256",
    },
    correct_option: "C",
    solution:
      "The difference between the possible values of the fraction more than 2 is 1/240.",
  },
  {
    _id: "3",
    topic: "Investment",
    category: "Numerical-Ability",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question:
      "A person invested ⅔ of his capital at the rate of 6%, ⅕ at the rate of 10%, and the remainder at the rate of 15%. If his actual income is 3,600, the capital will be:",
    options: {
      A: "Rs. 5000",
      B: "Rs. 2500",
      C: "Rs. 7500",
      D: "Rs. 4500",
    },
    correct_option: "D",
    solution:
      "The correct capital is Rs. 45,000. The provided options were wrong.",
  },
  {
    _id: "4",
    topic: "Exponents",
    category: "Numerical-Ability",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question: "If 8^(x+1) + 8^(1-x) = 20, then x = ?",
    options: {
      A: "¼, -¼",
      B: "½, -½",
      C: "⅓, -⅓",
      D: "⅕, -⅕",
    },
    correct_option: "C",
    solution: "The value of x is ⅓ or -⅓.",
  },
  {
    _id: "5",
    topic: "Percentage",
    category: "Numerical-Ability",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question:
      "At an academic institution, the break-up of holidays in 2016 was as follows:\n- 52 weekends\n- 30 days of summer vacation (includes 4 weekends)\n- Autumn and Winter Breaks of 10 days each (inclusive of 1 weekend)\n- 14 holidays on special occasions (including 1 Saturday and 1 Sunday)\nWhat was the percentage (correct up to two decimal places) of the number of holidays?",
    options: {
      A: "45.90%",
      B: "42.08%",
      C: "42.19%",
      D: "43.73%",
    },
    correct_option: "B",
    solution: "The percentage of holidays was 42.08%.",
  },
  {
    _id: "6",
    topic: "Averages",
    category: "Numerical-Ability",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question:
      "In a family of 10 adults and a few minors, the average consumption of flour is 12 kg. If the average consumption per adult and minor is 15 kg and 7 kg, respectively, what is the number of minors?",
    options: {
      A: "6",
      B: "7",
      C: "5",
      D: "8",
    },
    correct_option: "A",
    solution: "The number of minors is 6.",
  },
  {
    _id: "7",
    topic: "Simple Interest and Compound Interest",
    category: "Numerical-Ability",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question:
      "A person lends 35% of his money at 12.5% per annum, 50% at 10% per annum, and the rest at 18% per annum. What would be the annual rate (approximately) if the interest is calculated on the whole sum?",
    options: {
      A: "13%",
      B: "14.5%",
      C: "13.5%",
      D: "13.75%",
    },
    correct_option: "C",
    solution:
      "The approximate annual rate is 13.475%, which is rounded to 13.5%.",
  },
  {
    _id: "8",
    topic: "Averages",
    category: "Numerical-Ability",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question:
      "The average weight of 6 people increases from 24 to 31.5 kg when one of them leaves the group and a new person joins. If the weight of the new person is 60 kg, what was the weight of the person who left?",
    options: {
      A: "22.5",
      B: "37.5",
      C: "15",
      D: "30",
    },
    correct_option: "C",
    solution: "The weight of the person who left was 15 kg.",
  },
  {
    _id: "9",
    topic: "Alloys",
    category: "Numerical-Ability",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question:
      "There are three types of alloys A, B, and C. The ratio of Copper, Tin, and Nickel in A, B, and C is 16:3:1, 15:3:2, and 14:5:1, respectively. If 10 kg, 15 kg, and 50 kg of A, B, and C are mixed together, what is the final ratio of Copper, Tin, and Nickel in the mixture?",
    options: {
      A: "217:65:18",
      B: "217:65:81",
      C: "217:56:18",
      D: "127:65:18",
    },
    correct_option: "A",
    solution:
      "The final ratio of Copper, Tin, and Nickel in the mixture is 217:65:18.",
  },
  {
    _id: "10",
    topic: "Profit and Loss",
    category: "Numerical-Ability",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    question:
      "Rahul bought a watch with a marked price of Rs. 1,875 at a 24% discount. He sold the watch to Rohit with a 28% profit. Rohit marked the price 25% higher than his cost price. Mohit bought the watch from Rohit at a 15% discount and then marked the price up by 50%. If Rahul had to pay Rs. 28.5 extra compared to what he initially paid, at what percent discount did Mohit sell the watch?",
    options: {
      A: "35%",
      B: "50%",
      C: "45%",
      D: "40%",
    },
    correct_option: "C",
    solution: "Mohit sold the watch at a 45% discount.",
  },
  {
    _id: "11",
    topic: "Time and Work",
    category: "Numerical-Ability",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question:
      "If a road of 210 km can be constructed by 540 workmen in 28 days, how many workmen are required to build a road of 150 km in 18 days?",
    options: {
      A: "600",
      B: "300",
      C: "650",
      D: "450",
    },
    correct_option: "A",
    solution: "The number of workmen required is 600.",
  },
  {
    _id: "12",
    topic: "Time Speed Distance",
    category: "Numerical-Ability",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question:
      "Two stations P and Q are 42 km apart. Rohit and Mohit start from P to Q at the speed of 6 km/h and 8 km/h, respectively. Mohit reaches Q first and returns to meet Rohit at R. Determine the distance between P and R in km.",
    options: {
      A: "30",
      B: "36",
      C: "33",
      D: "27",
    },
    correct_option: "B",
    solution: "The distance between P and R is 36 km.",
  },
  {
    _id: "13",
    topic: "Time Speed Distance",
    category: "Numerical-Ability",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question:
      "The railway platform at a certain station is 248 m long. In how many seconds is it cleared by the express train, which is 127 m long and travels at a speed of 150 km/h?",
    options: {
      A: "9",
      B: "12",
      C: "8",
      D: "10",
    },
    correct_option: "A",
    solution: "The express train clears the platform in 9 seconds.",
  },
  {
    _id: "14",
    topic: "Ratio and Proportion",
    category: "Numerical-Ability",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question:
      "Nookaraju and Bhavana have their salaries in the ratio 7:3. As Bhavana is skilled, she got an increment of 5,000. But Nookaraju's performance is not up to the mark, and he got a decrement of 1,000. If their present salaries are in the ratio of 1:1, what is Nookaraju's present salary?",
    options: {
      A: "8,500",
      B: "9,500",
      C: "15,000",
      D: "10,500",
    },
    correct_option: "B",
    solution: "Nookaraju's present salary is Rs. 9,500.",
  },
  {
    _id: "15",
    topic: "Mensuration",
    category: "Numerical-Ability",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question:
      "The perimeter of a regular hexagon with an area of (21 sqrt{3} , \text{cm}^2) is:",
    options: {
      A: "12 ( sqrt{3} )",
      B: "6 ( sqrt{14} )",
      C: "9 ( sqrt{3} )",
      D: "7 ( sqrt{15} )",
    },
    correct_option: "B",
    solution: "The perimeter of the hexagon is (6 sqrt{14}, \text{cm}).",
  },
  {
    _id: "16",
    topic: "Elementary Statistics",
    category: "Numerical-Ability",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    question:
      "If the first quartile ( \\(Q_1 = 28)\\) and the third quartile ( \\(Q_3 = 42)\\), then the coefficient of quartile deviation is:",
    options: {
      A: " (\\(\\frac{1}{5}\\))",
      B: "(\\(\\frac{1}{3}\\))",
      C: "(\\(\\frac{1}{4}\\))",
      D: "(\\(\\frac{1}{2}\\))",
    },
    correct_option: "A",
    solution:
      "The coefficient of quartile deviation is ( \\(\\frac{1}{5}\\) ).",
  },
  {
    _id: "17",
    topic: "Profit and Loss",
    category: "Numerical-Ability",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question:
      "A farmer purchased a trolley and a tractor for Rs. 8,00,000. He sold the tractor at a profit of 30% and the trolley at a loss of 10%. In this deal, he gained a profit of 3%. What is the ratio of the cost price of the tractor and trolley?",
    options: {
      A: "54:31",
      B: "27:13",
      C: "13:27",
      D: "13:54",
    },
    correct_option: "C",
    solution:
      "The ratio of the cost price of the tractor and trolley is 13:27.",
  },
  // {
  //   _id: "18",
  //   topic: "Profit and Loss",
  //   category: "Numerical-Ability",
  //   difficulty: "Medium",
  //   question:
  //     "The marked price of a marker is (5 \frac{5}{9})% higher than its cost price. A discount of (5 \frac{5}{19})% is given on its marked price. Find the difference between the cost price and the selling price.",
  //   correct_option: "A",
  //   solution: "The difference between the cost price and selling price is 1.",
  // },
  {
    _id: "19",
    category: "Verbal-Ability",
    topic: "Error Identification",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    question:
      "Parts of the given sentence have been given as options. One of them contains a grammatical error. Select the option that has the error.<br><br>A university training enables a graduate seeing things as they are, and to disentangle a plethora of thoughts.",
    options: {
      A: "to disentangle a plethora of thoughts",
      B: "a graduate seeing things as they are",
      C: "to go right to the point",
      D: "A university training enables",
    },
    correct_option: "B",
    solution:
      "The correct answer is: 'a graduate seeing things as they are'. The correct construction would be 'a graduate to see things as they are.'",
  },
  {
    _id: "20",
    category: "Verbal-Ability",
    topic: "Error Identification",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    question:
      "Identify the part of the sentence that has an error.<br><br>I like to sit at the window for hours and see children playing in the park.",
    options: {
      A: "I like to sit at",
      B: "The window for hours",
      C: "In the park",
      D: "And see children playing",
    },
    correct_option: "D",
    solution:
      "The correct answer is: 'And see children playing'. The correct form would be 'And watch children playing'.",
  },
  {
    _id: "21",
    category: "Verbal-Ability",
    topic: "Sentence Correction",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question:
      "Each sentence contains four underlined phrases. Three of these phrases have been correctly used, and one has been incorrectly used. Choose the phrase (from option) which best replaces the wrong phrase in the sentence.<br><br>Explorers embody the finest spirit in human nature which is to seek new challenges, discover new worlds, and create new frontiers, and one such rare achievement of the indomitable spirit is the ascending of Mount Everest by Hillary and Tenzing.",
    options: {
      A: "Finer spirits",
      B: "By the dominant",
      C: "To have sought",
      D: "The ascent",
    },
    correct_option: "D",
    solution:
      "The correct answer is: 'The ascent'. The phrase 'the ascending' should be replaced with 'the ascent'.",
  },
  {
    _id: "22",
    category: "Verbal-Ability",
    topic: "Sentence Completion",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question:
      "Select the most appropriate set of options to fill in the blanks.<br><br>Bill Gates dropped out from Harvard within a year. Then he formed Microsoft. 'Microsoft’s (A) _______ is a computer on every desk and Microsoft software on every computer.' Bill is a visionary and works very hard to (B) ______ his vision. His belief in high intelligence and hard work had put him where he is today. He does not believe in mere luck or God’s grace, but just hard work and (C) ______. His beliefs are so powerful that they have helped him increase his wealth and establish his (D) ______ in the industry.",
    options: {
      A: "(A) Symbol (B) attain (C) investment (D) control",
      B: "(A) Target (B) progress (C) frankness (D) importance",
      C: "(A) Logo (B) believe (C) blessings (D) esteem",
      D: "(A) Vision (B) achieve (C) competitiveness (D) monopoly",
    },
    correct_option: "D",
    solution:
      "The correct answer is: (A) Vision (B) achieve (C) competitiveness (D) monopoly.",
  },
  {
    _id: "23",
    category: "Verbal-Ability",
    topic: "Sentence Completion",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question:
      "Select the most appropriate set of options to fill in the blanks.<br><br>Mexico is home to more species of oak than any country in the world, though many of them are (1) ___ . In the case of the arroyo oak, as it is known, the species now faces a particularly (2) __ problem. Though plenty of trees aged more than 100 years can be found, locals (3) __ that in recent years there had been no seedlings that have sprouted from their acorns in sight. For some reason, the trees had (4) __ stopped reproducing.",
    options: {
      A: "1-B, 2-B, 3-C, 4-D",
      B: "1-A, 2-B, 3-A, 4-D",
      C: "1-D, 2-A, 3-B, 4-C",
      D: "1-C, 2-D, 3-B, 4-B",
    },
    correct_option: "A",
    solution:
      "The correct answer is: 1-B (threatened), 2-B (troubling), 3-C (noticed), 4-D (simply).",
  },
  {
    _id: "24",
    category: "Verbal-Ability",
    topic: "Idioms and Phrases",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question:
      "Choose the most appropriate set of idioms that would fit in the blanks and complete the text given here.<br><br>Sadhguru, the famous mystic, made several attempts to improve the nation’s rivers a few years back. The government of India (1) _______ some of his ideas, which he had incorporated in the union budget. However, his solutions were not received well in (2) __________. After bearing these criticisms, he decided not to provide any more solutions but to focus on the problem itself. His strongest message? We cannot (3) _______ to the fact that soil is being rejected, whether it is concrete paving, denuding vegetation, use of chemicals, etc. The soil is not being given the respect it deserves. He has now (4) ______ of the politicians, the bureaucrats, and the technocrats to find and execute solutions.",
    options: {
      A: "Reflected upon, certain quarters, turn a blind eye, put the ball in the court",
      B: "Reflected upon, a chunk of, turned the other way, gave up on",
      C: "Reflected upon, a cross section, turned the other way, given up",
      D: "Thought aloud, certain section, turn a deaf ear, taken a back seat",
    },
    correct_option: "A",
    solution:
      "The correct answer is: Reflected upon, certain quarters, turn a blind eye, put the ball in the court.",
  },
  {
    _id: "25",
    category: "Verbal-Ability",
    topic: "Idioms and Phrases",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    question:
      "Choose the sentence in which the underlined idiom has been used appropriately.<br><br>1. The way Sanya’s obsessing over one doorknob when they’re renovating the entire house makes one think that she can’t see the wood in the trees.<br>2. Marcus is so focused on product details that he can’t see the wood for the trees when it comes to the overall needs of the company.<br>3. The safety officer can’t see the wood for the trees because she doesn’t know which way to look.<br>4. Raman always argues on the silliest topics, it’s like he can’t see the tree for the woods.",
    options: {
      A: "Option 1",
      B: "Option 2",
      C: "Option 3",
      D: "Option 4",
    },
    correct_option: "B",
    solution:
      "The correct answer is: 'Marcus is so focused on product details that he can’t see the wood for the trees.'",
  },
  {
    _id: "26",
    category: "Verbal-Ability",
    topic: "Idioms and Phrases",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question:
      "Four idioms are given below. Choose their sequence that would fill in the blanks and complete the text here.<br><br>Instead of the big crowd we expected, people arrived in _____ at the musical night. Alpana Alam is a rising star and is usually able to _____. Even before the interval it was obvious that the event was _____. Despite all this, Alpana herself was ______.<br><br>1. A dead duck<br>2. Bring the house down<br>3. Full of beans<br>4. Dribs and drabs",
    options: {
      A: "1234",
      B: "4231",
      C: "4213",
      D: "1342",
    },
    correct_option: "C",
    solution:
      "The correct answer is: 4213 (Dribs and drabs, Bring the house down, A dead duck, Full of beans).",
  },
  // {
  //   _id: "9",
  //   category: "Verbal-Ability",
  //   topic: "Para Jumble",
  //   difficulty: "Hard",
  //   question:
  //     "Given below is a paragraph with five sentences, which are presented in a jumbled order. Write down the best order which would form a meaningful, unified and coherent paragraph.<br><br>1. We need to listen and act upon what birds are telling us, as they disappear ever faster of about 11,000 species and spanning the globe, the populations of half of them are falling, while just 6% are increasing.<br>2. Birds truly are the canary in the coal mine – as indicators for the health of our planet, given their sensitivity to ecosystem changes, their ubiquity around the planet, and how well studied they are.<br>3. Conservation efforts have been successful at rescuing individual species in specific locations from the brink, but political will and funding are needed to reverse the global decline.<br>4. Bird populations are affected by the damage caused by human activity, from the destruction of wild habitat, the climate crisis, the pesticides and other pollution, to over-hunting and impacts of alien species and diseases.<br>5. Billions of birds have been lost in recent decades in North America and Europe alone, and while there are more species in the tropics, a higher proportion are at risk of extinction in the temperate and largely richer nations.",
  //   correct_option: "BADEC",
  //   solution: "The correct order is: BADEC.",
  // },
  {
    _id: "27",
    category: "Verbal-Ability",
    topic: "Sentence Arrangement",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question:
      "The four sentence (S1 to S4) paragraph below, Sentences S1 and S4 are given. From the options P, Q, R and S, choose the appropriate sentences for this respectively.<br><br>S1. Placebos are essential to the design of reliable clinical trials.<br>S2. ___________<br>S3. ___________<br>S4. Red, Yellow and orange are associated with a stimulant effect, while blue and green are related to tranquilizing effect, says Dr. A. J. de Craen.",
    options: {
      A: "Such studies have found that even the color of pills made a difference in placebo results.",
      B: "Their once-surprising effect on participants has become the focus of many studies.",
      C: "Another argument says that by prescribing a placebo to placate a patient, the correct diagnosis of a serious ailment might be postponed.",
      D: "At one time, placebos were only used in experiments as a control.",
    },
    correct_option: "QP",
    solution: "The correct answer is: QP.",
  },
  {
    _id: "28",
    category: "Reasoning-Ability",
    topic: "Letter Series",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question:
      "Identify the letter-cluster that does not belong to the following series.<br><br>CX, GT, EV, DW, HS, ZA, MN, UF",
    options: {
      A: "ZA",
      B: "UF",
      C: "HS",
      D: "MN",
    },
    correct_option: "C",
    solution:
      "The correct answer is 'HS' because it does not follow the pattern followed by the others.",
  },
  {
    _id: "29",
    category: "Reasoning-Ability",
    topic: "Letter Analogy",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question:
      "Four pairs of letter-clusters have been given, out of which three are alike in some manner and one is different. Select the one that is different.<br><br>1. TMKOLFXOY : TOMKLFXOY<br>2. PVMSYGCXN : VSPMYCGNX<br>3. XDSWZOIVK : XWSDZIKOV<br>4. FCHVOTFGW : VHFCOFGTW",
    options: {
      A: "TMKOLFXOY : TOMKLFXOY",
      B: "PVMSYGCXN : VSPMYCGNX",
      C: "XDSWZOIVK : XWSDZIKOV",
      D: "FCHVOTFGW : VHFCOFGTW",
    },
    correct_option: "A",
    solution:
      "The correct answer is 'TMKOLFXOY : TOMKLFXOY' because it does not follow the rearrangement pattern of the other pairs.",
  },
  {
    _id: "30",
    category: "Reasoning-Ability",
    topic: "Blood Relations",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question:
      "In a certain code language:<br>• P & Q means P is the son of Q<br>• P @ Q means P is the mother of Q<br>• P % Q means P is the brother of Q<br>• P # Q means P is the husband of Q<br><br>Based on the above, how is K related to Q if ‘K % G & T # V @ S @ N % Q’?",
    options: {
      A: "Father",
      B: "Father's brother",
      C: "Mother's brother",
      D: "Brother",
    },
    correct_option: "C",
    solution:
      "The correct answer is 'Mother’s Brother'. By following the relationships step-by-step, K is revealed to be Q’s mother’s brother.",
  },
  {
    _id: "31",
    category: "Reasoning-Ability",
    topic: "Decision Making",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    question:
      "Following are the criteria for the post of a Senior Engineer in an electrical company:<br>1. Be in the range of 22 to 35 years as on 8 March 2017<br>2. Be a graduate in Electrical Engineering with at least 60% marks<br>3. Have passed the recruitment test with a minimum of 70% marks<br>4. Be willing to deposit an amount of Rs 45000 as part of the agreement<br><br>If a candidate fulfills all the criteria except (b) above, but has appeared in the last semester and has secured at least 65% in the first semester, refer to the director.<br>If a candidate fulfills all the criteria except (d) above, but is willing to pay at least 50% of the deposit amount, and has secured 70% marks in graduation, refer to the chairman.<br><br>Based on the above-mentioned criteria, take a decision for the following application.<br><br>Raini D’Souza is an Electrical Engineering graduate with 70% marks. She was born on 4 March 1982 and has obtained 76% marks in the recruitment test.",
    options: {
      A: "Not to be selected",
      B: "Data is incomplete",
      C: "To be selected",
      D: "Case to be referred to the chairman",
    },
    correct_option: "D",
    solution:
      "The correct answer is 'Case to be referred to the chairman' as Raini fulfills all the criteria except the deposit condition.",
  },
  {
    _id: "32",
    category: "Reasoning-Ability",
    topic: "Statement and Course of Action",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    question:
      "Read the given statement and courses of action carefully and decide which of the given courses of action logically follows:<br><br>Statement: Despite the hostel warnings, the student was caught exploding crackers secretly on the hostel campus during a birthday celebration.<br><br>Course of actions:<br>1. All the crackers should be taken away from the students and they should be threatened not to do it again.<br>2. The students should be severely punished for this wrong act.",
    options: {
      A: "Either I or II follows",
      B: "Only II follows",
      C: "Neither I nor II follows",
      D: "Only I follows",
    },
    correct_option: "A",
    solution:
      "The correct answer is 'Either I or II follows'. Both actions are feasible courses that could follow logically from the given statement.",
  },
  {
    _id: "33",
    category: "Reasoning-Ability",
    topic: "Ages",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    question:
      "20 years ago, Mohita was 22 years old. How old was she X years ago?",
    options: {
      A: "X – 42",
      B: "42",
      C: "42 – X",
      D: "62 – X",
    },
    correct_option: "C",
    solution:
      "The correct answer is '42 – X'. To find out how old Mohita was X years ago, you subtract X from 42, her current age.",
  },
  {
    _id: "34",
    category: "Reasoning-Ability",
    topic: "Statements and Conclusions",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    question:
      "A question is given followed by two statements labeled I and II. Identify which of the statements is sufficient to answer the question.<br><br>Question: Let P be the total number of males and Q be the total number of females in a family. What is the difference between P and Q?<br><br>Statements:<br>1. Vipraja has six daughters, who have a brother, Vipraja is the wife of Shantanu.<br>2. Shantanu is the father of six daughters. Kiran’s mother Vipraja is married to Shantanu. Khan is a male.",
    options: {
      A: "Statement I alone is sufficient",
      B: "Either statement I alone or statement II alone is sufficient",
      C: "Both statements I and II together are necessary",
      D: "Statement II alone is sufficient",
    },
    correct_option: "A",
    solution:
      "The correct answer is 'Statement I alone is sufficient' as it provides enough information to deduce the difference between P and Q.",
  },
];

// export const august_20_2023 = [
//   {
//     _id: "1",
//     topic: "LCM and HCF",
//     category: "Numerical-Ability",
//     difficulty: "Easy",
//     question: "What is the sum of LCM and HCF of 5/18, 35/9, and 15/63?",
//     options: {
//       A: "1475/252",
//       B: "1475/126",
//       C: "625/252",
//       D: "625/126",
//     },
//     correct_option: "B",
//     solution: "The sum of LCM and HCF is 1475/126.",
//   },
//   {
//     _id: "2",
//     topic: "Reciprocal and Fractions",
//     category: "Numerical-Ability",
//     difficulty: "Medium",
//     question:
//       "The reciprocal of a fraction is more than itself by 21/240. How much is the difference between the possible values of the fraction more than 2?",
//     options: {
//       A: "1/15",
//       B: "1/16",
//       C: "1/240",
//       D: "1/256",
//     },
//     correct_option: "C",
//     solution:
//       "The difference between the possible values of the fraction more than 2 is 1/240.",
//   },
//   {
//     _id: "3",
//     topic: "Investment",
//     category: "Numerical-Ability",
//     difficulty: "Medium",
//     question:
//       "A person invested ⅔ of his capital at the rate of 6%, ⅕ at the rate of 10%, and the remainder at the rate of 15%. If his actual income is 3,600, the capital will be:",
//     options: {
//       A: "Rs. 5000",
//       B: "Rs. 2500",
//       C: "Rs. 7500",
//       D: "Rs. 4500",
//     },
//     correct_option: "D",
//     solution:
//       "The correct capital is Rs. 45,000. The provided options were wrong.",
//   },
//   ,
//   {
//     _id: "16",
//     topic: "Elementary Statistics",
//     category: "Numerical-Ability",
//     difficulty: "Easy",
//     question:
//       "If the first quartile ( \\(Q_1 = 28)\\) and the third quartile ( \\(Q_3 = 42)\\), then the coefficient of quartile deviation is:",
//     options: {
//       A: " (\\(\\frac{1}{5}\\))",
//       B: "(\\(\\frac{1}{3}\\))",
//       C: "(\\(\\frac{1}{4}\\))",
//       D: "(\\(\\frac{1}{2}\\))",
//     },
//     correct_option: "A",
//     solution:
//       "The coefficient of quartile deviation is ( \\(\\frac{1}{5}\\) ).",
//   },
//   {
//     _id: "17",
//     question: "Another Question 2",
//     topic: "LCM and HCF",
//     category: "Numerical-Ability",
//     difficulty: "Medium",
//     options: {
//       A: "Option A",
//       B: "Option B",
//       C: "Option C",
//       D: "Option D",
//     },
//     correct_option: "D",
//     solution: "The sum of LCM and HCF is 1475/126.",
//   },
//   {
//     _id: "17",
//     question: "Another Question 2",
//     topic: "LCM and HCF",
//     category: "Numerical-Ability",
//     difficulty: "Hard",
//     options: {
//       A: "Option A",
//       B: "Option B",
//       C: "Option C",
//       D: "Option D",
//     },
//     correct_option: "D",
//     solution: "The sum of LCM and HCF is 1475/126.",
//   },
// ];
